A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33; 276.7 Cubic Feet 725 document boxes
  - Real Estate, 1977-1981; 23; 20.13 Cubic Feet 49 letter document boxes, 2 legal document boxes, 1 tall legal box
    - Olohana Corporation, 6
      - Water (Box 408, Folder 2-3)
    - Pocantico Hills, 7
      - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 409, Folder 2)
      - Future (Box 409, Folder 3)
      - National Historic Landmark - Brochure, 1980 (Box 409, Folder 4)
      - National Historic Landmark - Brochure, 1977 (Box 409, Folder 5-6, Box 410, Folder 1)
      - National Historic Landmark - Sleepy Hollow Restoration (Box 410, Folder 2)
      - National Historic Landmark - Printed Material (Box 410, Folder 3)
      - C.W. Frye - Pocantico Development-Frank Cross (Box 411, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Open in 2029
      - Future - Frye, Clayton W. (Box 411, Folder 2)
      - Land Use Study - Sasaki, 1981 (Box 411, Folder 3)
      - National Historic Landmark - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1977-1981 (Box 411, Folder 4)
      - National Historic Landmark, 1977-1981 (Box 412, Folder 1-2)
      - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Pocantico Recommendations (Box 412, Folder 3-4, Box 413, Folder 1-2)
      - Housing Plans, 1981 (Box 413, Folder 3)
      - National Park Service (Box 413, Folder 4)
      - National Park Service - A-Z (Box 413, Folder 5)
      - Pocantico Committee (Box 414, Folder 1)
      - Property (Box 414, Folder 2)
      - Property - Buttermilk Hill (Box 414, Folder 3)
      - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Agreements (Box 414, Folder 4)
      - Public Affairs (Box 415, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center/Rockefeller Center, Inc., 8
      - Rockefeller Center - Guidelines of Business (Box 415, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Center - A-K (Box 415, Folder 3-5)
      - Rockefeller Center - M-Z (Box 416, Folder 1-3)
      - Cushman and Wakefield, Inc. (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - Finances (Box 418, Folder 1-2)
      - Finances-Investments (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - Minutes-Meetings (Box 419, Folder 1-3)
      - Miscellaneous Meetings (Box 419, Folder 4)
      - Printed Material (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - RCTV (Box 420, Folder 2)
      - Radio City Music Hall - A-Z (Box 420, Folder 3)
      - Radio City Music Hall - Printed Material (Box 420, Folder 4)
      - Radio City Music Hall Productions Inc. (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - Real Estate Development Committee (Box 421, Folder 1)
      - Rock-Celanese (Box 421, Folder 2)
      - Rock-Flower, Inc. (Box 421, Folder 3)
      - Rock-Morris (Box 421, Folder 4)
      - Rock-Time (Box 421, Folder 5, Box 422, Folder 1)
      - Rock-Uris (Box 422, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Brothers - Leases (Box 417, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Center Construction Corp. (Box 422, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller Center Development Corp. (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller Center Development Corp. - A-Z (Box 422, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller Center Management Corp. (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Rockresorts, 9
      - Rockresorts - A-Z (Box 423, Folder 1-3)
      - Finances (Box 423, Folder 4)
      - Cerromar Beach Hotel (Box 423, Folder 5)
      - Dorado Beach (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - Kapalua Bay Hotel (Box 424, Folder 2-3)
      - Kapalua Bay Hotel - Printed Material (Box 424, Folder 4)
      - Halekulani Hotel (Box 424, Folder 5)
      - Little Dix Bay - General (Box 425, Folder 1)
      - Little Dix Bay - A-Z (Box 425, Folder 2-3)
      - Little Dix Bay - Finances (Box 425, Folder 4, Box 426, Folder 1-2)
      - Little Dix Bay - Printed Matter (Box 426, Folder 3)
      - Little Dix Bay - Virgin Gorda Marina (Box 426, Folder 4)
      - Mauna Kea (Box 426, Folder 5)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - A-C (Box 426, Folder 6)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - D-Z (Box 427, Folder 1-2)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Blueprints and Maps (Box 427, Folder 3-4, Box 428, Folder 1)
      - Mauna Kea - Chapel (Box 428, Folder 2)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Finances (Box 428, Folder 3)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Sale - A-Z (Box 428, Folder 4)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Sale (Box 429, Folder 1-2, Box 430, Folder 1)
      - Mauna Kea Fairways (Box 431, Folder 1)
      - Memos (Box 431, Folder 2)
      - Minutes-Meetings (Box 417, Folder 3, Box 430, Folder 2-4)
      - Suicide Six (Box 431, Folder 3)
      - Mt. Tom and Suicide Six (Box 431, Folder 4)
      - Printed Matter (Box 431, Folder 5)
      - Victoria International Corp. (Box 432, Folder 1-3)
      - Victoria International Corp. - Reports (Box 432, Folder 4, Box 433, Folder 1)
    - Offers, 10
      - Offers - A-F (Box 433, Folder 4)
      - Offers - G-N (Box 434, Folder 1-3)
      - Offers - O-Z (Box 435, Folder 1-3)
      - Yerba Buena Center (Box 435, Folder 4)
  - Religion, 1977-1981; 24; 4.56 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes
    - Religion - A-Z, 1
      - Religion - A-E (Box 436, Folder 1-6)
      - Religion - F-N (Box 437, Folder 1-5)
      - Religion - O-Z (Box 438, Folder 1-4)
      - Riverdale Center of Religious Research (Box 439, Folder 1)
      - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks (Box 439, Folder 2)
      - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Printed Matter (Box 439, Folder 3)
      - Agape (Box 439, Folder 4)
      - Appeal of Conscience Foundation (Box 439, Folder 5)
      - American Friends Service Committee (Box 440, Folder 1)
      - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'raith (Box 440, Folder 2)
      - Christian Science Association (Box 440, Folder 3)
      - Council on Religion and International Affairs (Box 440, Folder 4)
      - The Genesis Project (Box 441, Folder 1-2)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 441, Folder 3)
      - Seamen's Church Institute (Box 441, Folder 4)
      - United Church of Christ (Box 441, Folder 5)
      - Zen Studies Society (Box 441, Folder 6, Box 442, Folder 1)
      - Zen Center, Rochester, NY (Box 442, Folder 2)
    - Churches, 2
      - Churches - A-Ch (Box 442, Folder 3-6)
      - Churches - Ci-S (Box 443, Folder 1-5)
      - Churches - S-Z (Box 444, Folder 1-3)
      - Brick Presbyterian Church (Box 444, Folder 4)
      - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine (Box 444, Folder 5)
      - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. (Box 444, Folder 6)
      - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. - Division of Church & Society (Box 445, Folder 1)
      - Riverside Church (Box 445, Folder 2)
      - Riverside Church - Contributions (Box 445, Folder 3)
      - St. John's Episcopal Church (Box 445, Folder 4)
      - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 445, Folder 5, Box 446, Folder 1)
    - Missions, 3
      - Missions - A-Z (Box 446, Folder 2)
      - New York City Mission Society (Box 446, Folder 3-4, Box 447, Folder 1)
      - New York City Mission Society - Printed Material (Box 447, Folder 2)
      - Quebec-Labrador Foundation (Box 447, Folder 3)
      - Quebec-Labrador Foundation - Printed Material (Box 447, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1981 (Bulk: 1977-1981); 1977-1981; 25; 75.57 Cubic Feet 198 containers
    - Rockefeller family - General, 1
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. (Box 447, Folder 5)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - A-Z (Box 448, Folder 1-2)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Gulfstream II Exchange Agreement (Box 448, Folder 3)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Flight Book (Box 448, Folder 4)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Board of Directors - Minutes/Meetings (Box 448, Folder 5)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Printed Material (Box 448, Folder 6)
      - Awards (Box 449, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Brothers - General Correspondence and Meetings (Box 449, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Brothers - Meetings (Box 449, Folder 3-5)
      - Rockefeller Family (Box 450, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Family Cousins (Box 450, Folder 2)
      - Fifth Generation (Box 450, Folder 3)
      - Trusts (Box 450, Folder 4)
    - Abby Rockefeller Mauze (and family), 2
      - Mauze, Abby Rockefeller (Box 453, Folder 2)
      - Estate (Box 453, Folder 3-5)
      - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Charitable Trust (Box 454, Folder 1)
      - J. Richardson Dilworth (Box 454, Folder 2)
      - Trusts (Box 454, Folder 3)
      - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Charitable Trust - Grants (Box 455, Folder 1)
      - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Charitable Trust - Grants - A-Z (Box 455, Folder 2-3)
      - Greenacre Foundation - A-Z (Box 455, Folder 4)
      - Greenacre Foundation - Board of Directors (Box 455, Folder 5)
      - Greenacre Foundation - Contributions (Box 456, Folder 1)
      - Greenacre Foundation - Greenacre Park - Finances (Box 456, Folder 2-3)
      - Greenacre Park - Insurance (Box 454, Folder 4)
      - Greenacre Park - Legal (Box 454, Folder 5)
      - Greenacre Park - Taxes (Box 454, Folder 6)
      - Greenacre Foundation - Minutes-Meetings (Box 456, Folder 4, Box 457, Folder 1-4)
      - Greenacre Foundation - Park Council (Box 457, Folder 5)
      - Greenacre Foundation - Requests (Box 460, Folder 1)
      - O'Neill, Abby (Gail) (Box 458, Folder 7)
      - O'Neill, Catherine, M. (Box 458, Folder 8)
      - O'Neill, David M. (Box 458, Folder 9)
      - O'Neill, Eliza Milton (Box 458, Folder 10)
      - O'Neill, George D. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Abby Milton) (Box 459, Folder 1)
      - O'Neill, George, Jr. (Box 459, Folder 2)
      - O'Neill, George, Jr. - Investments (Box 459, Folder 3)
      - O'Neill, Mr. and Mrs. Grover III and Laura K. Simpson (Box 459, Folder 4)
      - O'Neill, Peter Meriwether (Box 459, Folder 5)
      - O'Neill, Wendy H. (Box 459, Folder 6)
      - Simpson, Abby Rockefeller (Box 608, Folder 5)
      - Simpson, William K. (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Trust (Box 608, Folder 6)
      - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton (Box 612, Folder 4)
      - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Charitable Income Trust (Box 612, Folder 5)
      - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Charitable Income Trust - A-Z (Box 612, Folder 6-8)
      - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Charitable Income Trust - University of Pennsylvania School of Veterinary (Box 613, Folder 1)
    - David Rockefeller (and family), 3
      - Rockefeller, David - A-E (Box 460, Folder 2-6)
      - Rockefeller, David - F-L (Box 461, Folder 1-5)
      - Rockefeller, David - M-S (Box 462, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, David - T-Z (Box 463, Folder 1)
      - Addresses-Remarks - A-C (Box 463, Folder 2-3)
      - Addresses-Remarks - D-R (Box 464, Folder 1-3)
      - Addresses-Remarks - S-Z (Box 465, Folder 1-2)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 465, Folder 3-4)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 465, Folder 5)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Japan-U.S. Businessmen's Conference (Box 465, Folder 6, Box 466, Folder 1)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Sample Speeches, 1979-1980 (Box 466, Folder 2-3)
      - Articles - A-K (Box 466, Folder 4, Box 467, Folder 1)
      - Articles - L-Z (Box 467, Folder 2)
      - Articles - Le Monde (Box 467, Folder 3-4, Box 468, Folder 1)
      - Autographs (Box 468, Folder 2)
      - Awards - A-Z (Box 468, Folder 3-4)
      - Biographical Notes - William Wing (Box 468, Folder 5, Box 469, Folder 1)
      - Boats (Box 469, Folder 2)
      - Christmas gifts (Box 469, Folder 3)
      - Council of the Americas (Box 469, Folder 4)
      - Dinners, Luncheons (Box 469, Folder 5)
      - Dinners, Luncheons - Overseas Development Council (Box 469, Folder 6)
      - Gifts (Box 470, Folder 1)
      - Giving Program (Box 470, Folder 2)
      - International Advisory Committee (Box 470, Folder 3)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-O (Box 470, Folder 4-7)
      - Invitations to Speak - P-Z (Box 471, Folder 1-2)
      - Invitations to Speak - Miscellaneous (Box 471, Folder 3)
      - Invitations (Box 471, Folder 4)
      - Jury Duty (Box 471, Folder 5)
      - Legal (Box 471, Folder 6)
      - Legal - Milbank, Tweed, Hadley and McCloy (Box 474, Folder 1)
      - Photographs (Box 471, Folder 7)
      - Politics (Box 472, Folder 1)
      - Property (Box 472, Folder 2)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 474, Folder 2)
      - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 472, Folder 3)
      - Property - Saint Barts (Box 472, Folder 4)
      - Radio/TV (Box 472, Folder 5)
      - Trips (Box 472, Folder 6)
      - Trusts (Box 474, Folder 3)
      - Work of Arts (Box 472, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 473, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Maine Coast Heritage Trust - Contributions (Box 473, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - General Correspondence (Box 473, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Pocantico Hills - Farm Project (Box 473, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Music Assistance Fund (Box 473, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, David, Jr. (Box 474, Folder 4)
      - Dulany-Quattrone (Box 452, Folder 5)
      - Kaiser, Walter, J. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Neva G. Rockefeller) (Box 452, Folder 6)
      - Growald, Paul Jeffrey (Mr. and Mrs.) (Eileen McGrath Rockefeller) (Box 452, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Eileen (Box 452, Folder 8)
      - Lindstrom, Christopher Rockefeller (Box 453, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Abby A. (Box 459, Folder 14)
      - Rockefeller, Abby A. - Investments (Clivus Multrum) (Box 458, Folder 11)
      - Rockefeller, Richard G. (Box 606, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Richard G. - Dune Fund (Box 606, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Rebecca Anderson (Box 607, Folder 5)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Sr. (and family), 4
      - Rockefeller, John D., Sr (Box 473, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, John D., Sr. - The John D. Rockefeller Family Cemetery Corp. (Box 474, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Laura Spelman (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (and family), 5
      - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Box 473, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller, Abby A. (Box 473, Folder 9)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - John D. Rockefeller, 3rd (and family), 6
      - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - A-Z (Box 475, Folder 1-2)
      - Addresses - A-J (Box 475, Folder 3)
      - Addresses - K-Z (Box 476, Folder 1)
      - Addresses - Miscellaneous (Box 476, Folder 2)
      - American Revolutionary Bicentennial (Box 476, Folder 3)
      - American Revolutionary Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era (Box 476, Folder 4)
      - Articles - A-Z (Box 476, Folder 5-6)
      - Autographs (Box 477, Folder 1)
      - Biography (Box 477, Folder 2)
      - Contact Sheets (Box 477, Folder 3)
      - Death (Box 477, Folder 4)
      - Death - Clippings (Box 477, Folder 5-6)
      - Death - Condolences - A-Be (Box 478, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - Bh-Ch (Box 479, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - Ch-D (Box 480, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - E-G (Box 481, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - H-J (Box 482, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - K-L (Box 483, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - M (Box 484, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - N-Pr (Box 485, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - Pr-R (Box 486, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - S (Box 487, Folder 1-3)
      - Death - Condolences - T-W (Box 488, Folder 1-4)
      - Death - Condolences - X-Z (Box 489, Folder 1)
      - Death - Condolences - to Nelson A. Rockefeller (NAR) (Box 489, Folder 2-3)
      - Death - Memorial Service (Box 489, Folder 4)
      - Death - Memorial Service Booklet (Box 490, Folder 1)
      - Death - Mass Cards (Box 499, Folder 1)
      - Death - Memorial Books (Box 499, Folder 2)
      - Death - Tributes (Box 499, Folder 3-4, Box 500, Folder 1)
      - Dinners (Box 490, Folder 2)
      - Estate (Box 532, Folder 6)
      - Invitations to Speak (Box 490, Folder 3)
      - Photos (Box 490, Folder 4)
      - Memorials (Box 490, Folder 5)
      - Property (Box 490, Folder 6)
      - Radio-TV (Box 490, Folder 7)
      - Works of Art - American Art Collection (Box 490, Folder 8)
      - Works of Art - American Art Collection - Purchases and Offers, 1974-1978 (Box 491, Folder 1)
      - Works of Art - American Art Collection - Loans and Declinations, 1974-1978 (Box 491, Folder 2)
      - Works of Art - American Art Collection - Richardson, Dr. E. P., 1974-1978 (Box 491, Folder 3)
      - Works of Art (Box 491, Folder 4)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - A-F (Box 491, Folder 5)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - G-Z (Box 492, Folder 1)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - Contributions (Box 492, Folder 2)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - Minutes-Meetings (Box 492, Folder 3-4, Box 493, Folder 1)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - The Third Sector (Box 493, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette (Box 493, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. - Na Champassak, Sisouk (Box 493, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. - Politics (Box 493, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. - Contributions - 1972-1973 (Box 692, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. - Contributions - 1974-1977 (Box 693, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. - Requests Declined - 1963-1972 (Box 693, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. - Requests Declined - 1973-1974 (Box 694, Folder 1-2)
      - Aldrich, Hope (Box 450, Folder 5)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Charitable Lead Trusts (Box 450, Folder 6)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Grants - A-Z (Box 450, Folder 7)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Giving Program (Box 450, Folder 8)
      - Dayton, Eric John (Box 451, Folder 7)
      - Dayton, Eric John - Charitable Lead Trust - A-Z (Box 451, Folder 9-12, Box 452, Folder 1)
      - Dayton, Mark Brandt (Mrs.) (Alida Davison Rockefeller) (Box 452, Folder 2)
      - Dayton - Giving Program (Box 452, Folder 3)
      - Dayton - Loans - Ms. Foundation for Education and Communications, Inc. (Box 452, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay (Box 494, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - Clippings (Box 494, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - Condolences sent to Jay on death of JDR 3rd (Box 494, Folder 4, Box 495, Folder 1-2, Box 496, Box 497, Folder 1-3, Box 498, Folder 1, Box 501, Box 502, Folder 1-4, Box 503)
      - Rockefeller, Sharon (Box 494, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Justin Aldrich (Box 511, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Sandra (Box 607, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Sandra - Community Fund No. 205 (Box 607, Folder 7)
      - Spencer, David Hooker (Box 608, Folder 7)
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller (and family), 7
      - Addresses (Box 500, Folder 2)
      - Agenda (Box 500, Folder 3)
      - Articles (Box 500, Folder 4)
      - Automobiles (Box 504, Folder 1)
      - Autographs (Box 504, Folder 2)
      - Awards (Box 504, Folder 3)
      - Awards - Citizens Committee for NYC. Inc. (Box 504, Folder 4)
      - Awards - Duke University (Box 504, Folder 5)
      - Awards - Pallisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 504, Folder 6)
      - Awards - United Hospital Fund of NY (Box 505, Folder 1)
      - Awards - Wings Club (Box 505, Folder 2)
      - Biography (Box 505, Folder 3, Box 506, Folder 1-2)
      - Books - Biography (Box 506, Folder 3)
      - Books - Book Purchase and Donations (Box 506, Folder 4)
      - Clippings (Box 506, Folder 5)
      - Clippings-Notes - Conservation (Box 506, Folder 6)
      - Clippings-Notes - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) (Box 506, Folder 7)
      - Clippings-Notes - Metaphysical (Box 507, Folder 1)
      - Clippings-Notes - Miscellaneous (Box 507, Folder 2)
      - Clippings (Box 507, Folder 3)
      - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 507, Folder 4)
      - Dinners - Hawaii, 1980 January 26 (Box 508, Folder 1)
      - Dinners - Princeton (Box 508, Folder 2)
      - Finances (Box 511, Folder 4)
      - Furnishings (Box 508, Folder 3)
      - Gifts (Box 508, Folder 4, Box 509, Folder 1)
      - Giving Program (Box 509, Folder 2)
      - Investments (Box 509, Folder 3)
      - Investments - A-H (Box 509, Folder 4-5)
      - Investments - I-Z (Box 510, Folder 1)
      - Investments - Grosvenor Publications Inc. (Box 510, Folder 2-4)
      - Legal (Box 511, Folder 5)
      - Invitations (Box 512, Folder 1)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-Z (Box 512, Folder 2)
      - Jewelry (Box 512, Folder 3)
      - Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 512, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln School Reunion - General (Box 512, Folder 5, Box 513, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln School Reunion - A-Z (Box 513, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln School Reunion - Transcript (Box 513, Folder 3-4)
      - Loans (Box 514, Folder 1)
      - Loans - Delafield, Walter B. (Box 514, Folder 2)
      - Mail (Box 514, Folder 3)
      - Memberships (Box 514, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Booklets (Box 514, Folder 5-6, Box 515, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Booklets - Gilbert, Benjamin D. (Box 515, Folder 2)
      - Memos (Box 515, Folder 3)
      - Personal (Box 515, Folder 4)
      - Photos (Box 515, Folder 5)
      - Photos - Karsh, Yousuf (Box 516, Folder 1)
      - Politics (Box 516, Folder 2)
      - Portraits (Box 516, Folder 3)
      - Property (Box 516, Folder 4)
      - Property - New York City - 620 Park Avenue (Box 516, Folder 5)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue (Box 516, Folder 6)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - A-K (Box 516, Folder 7)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - L-Z (Box 517, Folder 1)
      - Property - Hawaii (Box 517, Folder 2)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Finances (Box 517, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Minutes-Meetings (Box 517, Folder 5)
      - Property - Hawaii - Hapuna Property (Box 518, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Hawaii - Kipahulu, Maui (Box 518, Folder 3)
      - Property - Hawaii - Kipahulu, Maui - Documents (Box 518, Folder 4)
      - Property - Hawaii - Kipahulu, Maui - Correspondence (Box 519, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Hawaii - Kipahulu, Maui - Appraisal, 1969 February (Box 519, Folder 3)
      - Purchases (Box 519, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - General (Box 520, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - A-Z (Box 520, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Finances (Box 520, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Legal (Box 521, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Long, Richard and Jane (Box 521, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Turner, Dennis and Shirlene (Box 521, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - Appreciation, 1965-1976 (Box 521, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits 1977 (Box 521, Folder 5)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits 1978-1981 (Box 522, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 523, Folder 1)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Marymount Secondary School Parcel (Box 523, Folder 2)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kent House (Box 523, Folder 3)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Rockwood Hall (Box 523, Folder 4)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Tarrytown (Box 523, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock (Box 697, Folder 4, Box 698, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - A-U (Box 698, Folder 2-6)
      - Property - Woodstock - V-Z (Box 699, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Elm Street Bridge (Box 699, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Low Cost Housing (Box 699, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 699, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Municipal Matters (Box 699, Folder 5, Box 700, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Woodstock - A-S (Box 709, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Woodstock - T-Z (Box 710, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Clippings-Articles (Box 710, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Elm Street Bridge (Box 710, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Finances (Box 710, Folder 4)